macgamestore.com 2019-05-27

# Privacy | macgamestore.com

## Privacy Policy

### Your Rights as a User

Inside Mac Games, Ltd, its subsidiaries and affiliated companies ("INSIDE MAC GAMES" or "we", "our", "us") provide this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of (i) the website located at www.macgamestore.com (the "Site"), including any services, features and content accessible or downloadable from the Site, and (ii) any other INSIDE MAC GAMES application, service or product licensed, downloaded or otherwise accessed by such users through third party websites or sources ((i) and (ii) collectively, the "Service"). This Privacy Policy in no way limits or restricts our collection of aggregate information or of other non-personal information. In this Privacy Policy, we refer to all information collected from or about you, including personal information and non-personal information, as "Your Information." 

### Quick Links:

  * Privacy Statement
  * What Personal Information We Collect
  * How We Use Your Personal Information
  * Disclosure of Personal Information
  * Children Policy
  * Consent (members only)
  * Cookie Statement
  * What are Cookies
  * Contact Us

* * *

### Privacy Statement (Personal Information)

**INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE:** Our primary goals in collecting and using information are to provide and improve the service, to administer and assist you in administering your Account on the service, and to provide you with a better experience with the service. We store and process information in the United States. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, we transfer your information to the United States and processes it there, which is required for the normal operation of the service. 

  * **Personal information** is information that specifically identifies an individual, including, but not limited to, an individual's name, email, credit card or other billing information and billing address (for the purposes of fulfilling a purchase order and licensing). Personal information does not include information that has been irreversibly anonymized or aggregated so that it can no longer enable us, whether in combination with other information or otherwise, to identify you.
  * **Non-personal information** is information that is not, on its own, personal information, such as an individual's IP, zip/postal code, but that may be considered part of an individual's personal information if combined with other identifiers in a way that enables identification of an individual. 

**What Personal Information We Collect**  
Depending on the services you use, we collect different kinds of personal information from or about you. In addition, we create a unique user ID to track your use of our services. This unique user ID is stored in connection with your information. 

  * **Information you provide** \- We collect information in any form you willingly enter data into. Such as your name and email during account registration. Any contact information you provide when asking us support questions. Signing up to our newsletter, or participating in public discussions and writing reviews.
  * **Information about payments** \- We collect billing information in connection with your transactions (such as, but not limited to, donations or the purchase of products) through the service. Paying with PayPal, we also collect account ids and verification data.
  * **Information about use of our services** \- When you visit our websites, we may collect general information about the type of device you use, your IP address, operating system, and the type of Internet browser being used. When you launch any of our applications, we collect information regarding your device type, operating system and version, carrier provider, IP address, whether you are using a point package, the game version, and unique device ID. We may gather some of this information automatically. Where available, our services may use GEO Location, your IP address, and other technologies to determine an approximate location to allow us to improve our products and services.
  * **Information from third parties** \- Some 3rd party services we use, may send us some other personal information you provided during use of their websites and services. Such as any information you provide on the "Store Support" website (managed by desk.com).
  * **Information from Facebook connect** \- If you use one of our applications and connect to your Facebook account within such application, you will be providing us with basic account information i.e., user ID, name, email, gender, birthday, profile picture URL. In addition, we will cache data we receive from the Facebook APIs to improve our user experience. 

**How We Use Your Personal Information**  
We use your personal information (in some cases, in conjunction with non-personal information) mainly to provide and improve the service. You have some control over the consent and use of this information within your account's "My Settings". 

  * **Communicating with you** \- The information you provide, helps us contact you about your account, actions, or other important cruicial matters. We may use your information to process and respond to your support requests when you contact us. Subject to your prior express consent, we may also use personal information to send you marketing communications, such as when a wishlist item goes on sale, or if new game content has been released for prior pruchases you made.
  * **Purchase licensing** \- Some information may be used in the fulfillment process for game purchases that return a license code. Some licensing is handled through third parties, and every effort is made to provide the bare minimum actual personal information. Most data is anonymized for the licensing transactions on your behalf to keep your personal information private.
  * **Promoting safety and security** \- We use personal information to help verify accounts and user activity, as well as to maintain security, such as by monitoring fraud and investigating suspicious or potentially illegal activity or violations of our terms or policies. Such processing is based on our legitimate interest in helping ensure the safety of our services.
  * **Analytics** \- We may combine your personal information with non-personal information and aggregate it with information collected from other users of the service to attempt to provide you with a better experience, to improve the quality and value of the service and to analyze and evaluate how the service is used. We may share aggregate information with third parties with whom we have a strategic relationship. The information shared with these third parties may be used for industry analysis and demographic profiling.
  * **Public presence** \- Foremost, your email address will **NOT be publicly visible** unless you provide it through communication to others. The optional Display Name will be visible to others if you participate in any public free speech channels such as Reviews, Comments ("Forum"). You are in control of how you wish your name to be displayed. You should be aware that any visitor to the Forum may read your postings. Furthermore, any information that you may post to a Forum, including your name or other Account profile information, will be disclosed and available to all viewers of that Forum, and will therefore no longer be private.

**PREFERENCES:** When you register for an Account or later access your Account, you may be able to adjust settings and preferences within your Account to choose whether to share and make publicly visible other pieces of your information, and the service may display your information based on the settings and preferences you choose. 

We encourage you to consider carefully what information to share as part of your Account profile and elsewhere in the service, and we recommend that you guard your anonymity and sensitive information and not use your real name as your Display Name, as that may allow other users of the service to identify you. Any information you choose to share should reflect how much you want other users of the service to know about you. You can review and revise your Account profile information at any time. 

During Sign Up using Facebook connect, many initial options are not presented, however you can adjust all account settings under your account "My Settings". 

**DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION:** We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate the service, to provide the service on our behalf, or to assist us in analyzing how the service is used. These third parties have access to your information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and may not use your information for any other purpose. We may also provide your information to our business partners or other trusted entities for the purpose of providing you with information on goods or services we believe will be of interest to you. 

We reserves the right to transfer your information in connection with a change or transfer of INSIDE MAC GAMES's ownership or a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. Prior notice will be sent to all registered accounts to opt-in or elect full deletion of personal data before such transfer occurs. 

We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of INSIDE MAC GAMES or any third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, illegal, unethical or legally actionable. 

**LOGGING DATA:** When you browse certain portions of the service, we may automatically collect and record standard user information and clickstream data about your visit (through the use of cookies and otherwise) as part of our analysis of the use of the service. For example, when you visit or request a web page from our server, we may record the IP address of the user's machine, the time, date and URL of the request and information about the browser being used, and other information regarding the visit, such as the pages visited on the service, the time spent on each page, any promotions clicked and any search terms used (collectively, "Log Data"). Log Data may be aggregated and used to monitor and analyze use of the service and to enable us to analyze traffic and trends, administer and improve the service, identify and keep track of errors and bugs, and gather broad demographic information to become more familiar with where visits to the service originate, how often the service is visited and what parts of the service are visited most often. 

We may also share such broad information with third party service providers assisting us with the foregoing and with our affiliates or advertisers. For example, some of this information may be collected and used so that when you visit the service again, it will recognize you and serve promotions and other information appropriate to your interests. We also use this information to verify that visitors to the service meet the criteria required to process their requests. We may link Log Data to personal information for tracking and analyzing our customers' use of the service to help improve the service, to tailor the service to their needs and to enforce the Terms of Use. 

Log Data is kept for a length of time that it is useful in the purposes of tracking down issues, or situations. Log Data is also used to facilitate better support for customers writing in with problems. 

**INVITE A FRIEND:** You may decide to provide us with another party's email address to allow us to contact and invite that party to visit or join the service or so that INSIDE MAC GAMES may facilitate your communication with such other party through methods of communication enabled by the service. Such email addresses will be used only for the purpose of sending email communications to the addressee. The email addresses are not added to any marketing databases or shared with any internal publishers or third parties. 

**GIFTING:** Sending a gift requires you to provide us with a contact email address. This allows us to contact and invite that party to claim their gift through a special claim code only sent to the gitfee. Such email addresses will be used only for the purpose of sending email communications to the addressee. The email addresses are not added to any marketing databases or shared with any internal publishers or third parties. 

**FORUM / COMMENTS:** We do not author, edit, endorse, or regularly monitor any Forum. You acknowledge and agree that INSIDE MAC GAMES has no responsibility for the accuracy or availability of information provided on any Forum by any user. INSIDE MAC GAMES reserves the right at any time, in its sole discretion, to remove any content that a user may post on any Forum and restrict their access to any Forum. 

**3RD PARTY LINKS:** The service may contain links to other websites and online services ("Linked Sites"), such as Facebook, Twitter, Disqus or Google. The fact that we link to a third party website or service is not an endorsement or representation of our affiliation with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy policies or practices. You acknowledge and agree that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such Linked Sites, and this Privacy Policy does not apply to such Linked Sites. The operators of Linked Sites may collect information about you, and may use and disclose that information. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of the Linked Sites that you use. 

**OPT-IN OPT-OUT POLICY:** We will not share your personal information in ways other than as described in this Privacy Policy unless you specifically elect to make your personal information available to third parties by selecting to "opt-in" in various places on the service. Your "opt-in" elections will not, however, _require_ us to share your personal information with any third parties. Further, you may "opt-out" of any prior elections and of receiving certain types of communications at any time through your Account Settings, or by contacting Store Support. 

**POLICY ON CHILDREN:** The service is not directed to children under the age of 14. We do not knowingly collect or solicit personally identifiable information from children under 14. If you are under 14, please do not attempt to register for an Account on the service or send any information about yourself to INSIDE MAC GAMES. If we become aware that a child under 14 has provided us with personal information, we will delete such information from our files. 

**SECURITY:** We take reasonable measures to protect your information from unauthorized access or against loss, misuse or alteration by third parties. Although we make good faith efforts to store the information collected on the service in a secure operating environment that is not available to the public, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of that information during its transmission or its storage on our systems. Further, while we attempt to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining access to this information. We do not warrant or represent that your Account or any of your information will be protected against, loss, misuse, or alteration by third parties. 

**CONSENT: (MEMBERS ONLY)** By registering for a Shopper Account that enables you to use the features of the store, place orders, to post to the Forums, and/or using the service (the "Account"), you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, and you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information and non-personal information by INSIDE MAC GAMES in accordance with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. The use of personal data is strictly necessary for the business to process orders and handle the account. Opting-out is available through voluntary account deletion. 

**VOLUNTARY ACCOUNT DELETION: (MEMBERS ONLY)** The option to delete personal information and site account data is available to members. Doing so removes all personal information. With that, all rights and privileges granted on the site are revoked, along with any and all product purchase rights and licenses. Refund policy will be revoked on all recent purchases. Once your personal information is removed, we are unable to verify any subsequent claims made by you against any prior possible purchases, now de-associated. 

* * *

### Cookie Statement

Like many websites (almost all), we use "cookie" technology to hold a session with you, manage your account access and to maintain a few site preferences (including cookie opt-outs). We do not use cookies to _collect_ personal information about you, but rather know it is you who has returned to us and how we should proceed to give you a rewarding experience. We reference cookies we issue with personal information that you provided to us (such as your account sign in session and preferences). This allows a fairly consistent experience. We may use cookies to improve the service and our other products and services. 

[Cookie Prefs](https://www.macgamestore.com/information/Cookies/) We provide some control over the cookies that exist on this site (some are required for base functionality). 

Your browser or device may also offer settings that allow you to choose whether browser cookies are set and to delete them. For more information about these controls and to exercise your cookie preferences, visit your browser or device's help material. If you choose to reject cookies, as noted above, you may not be able to use certain features of our websites and services. 

**KNOWN 1ST PARTY COOKIES LIST:**

Name| Type| Length| Type  
Length| Details  
---|---|---|---|---  
PHPSESSID | Essential | Session | Essential  
Session | Global. Core service key to handle any and all temporary application session data.  
PHPSLUG | Essential | Session | Essential  
Session | Global. Core service id tied directly to PHPSESSID, not to a specific user.  
BinkU | Essential | 6 month | Essential  
6 month | Members only. Signed In session identifier and security token.  
DinkU_# | Essential | 60 day | Essential  
60 day | Members only. Secondary security token for members who have opted into 2-factor authorization.  
PrefsU | Essential* | 1 year | Essential*  
1 year | Basic site usage prefs, like currency choice, and product results in list or tile. Does not contain any personally identifying information. *Essential if you wish to opt-in/out of specific cookie systems instead of all.  
ARSID | Affiliate | 30 day | Affiliate  
30 day | Maintains affiliate referral link ID (our internal affiliate system) to grant commissions from purchases made by users coming to us from an external affiliate website. Identifies the affiliate, not the user. Without this cookie, affiliates suffer.  
 **Please allow these** for the sake of your favorite affiliate sites!  
UTMWeb | Analytics | 30 day | Analytics  
30 day | Internal UTM tracking cookie from our own newsletter, wishlist sale notice, and product notification email campaigns. So we know if a campaign was worth bothering doing again. (phasing out)  
  
**3RD PARTY COOKIES LIST:**

Name | Type| Length| Party | Type  
Party | Domain | Details  
---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
__utm* | Analytics| Mixed| Google | Analytics  
Mixed  
Google  
.google.com | .google.com | Google Analytics cookies used to distinguish users on a website to generate statistical information about their use of the website.  
(various) | Social| Mixed| Facebook | Social  
Mixed  
Facebook  
.facebook.com | .facebook.com | Facebook social media sharing buttons come with a plethora of various cookies they set and maintain. Which appear to change often, and in quantity. To find out more about them, please visit Facebook and read their cookie policy.  
(various) | Social| Mixed| Twitter | Social  
Mixed  
Twitter  
.twitter.com | .twitter.com | Twitter social media sharing buttons also come with various cookies they set and maintain. To find out more about them, please visit Twitter and read their cookie policy.  
(numerous) | Comments| Mixed| Disqus | Comments  
Mixed  
Disqus  
.disqus.com  
.pippio.com  
.rezync.com | .disqus.com  
.pippio.com  
.rezync.com | Disqus is a plug-in comment system found on the bottom of Product detail pages, and articles. Their cookies are vast, numerous, and ranging from multiple other 4th parties. The only way to opt out of these, is to fully [Disable Disqus](https://www.macgamestore.com/information/Cookies/).  
  
**WHAT ARE COOKIES:**

"Cookie"| A cookie is a small string of text that we transfer to your web browser for temporary or long term storage. Cookies are used to store and receive identifiers and other information on computers, phones and other devices.  
---|---  
"Session"| A session cookie (strictly required) enables certain features of the service and is deleted from your computer when you close your browser or leave the service after a period of time.  
"Persistent"| A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the service. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions.  
"Accepting"| Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your web browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If your browser is set to refuse all cookies, however, many features of the service may not function properly, and you will never be able to maintain a Shopper Account.  
  
This Cookie Statement does not apply to the cookies, applications, technologies, or websites that are owned and/or operated by third parties, or such third parties practices, even if they use or access our technology to store or collect information. To understand how third parties use cookies, please review their privacy and cookie policies. 

* * *

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY:** INSIDE MAC GAMES reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to change or modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the changed or modified version of the Privacy Policy on the Site. Any such changes or modifications will be effective immediately upon posting. If we make any notable changes to this Privacy Policy, we will change the Last Revised date below. 

**CONTACT:** If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us using our Support section. 

_Last Updated: May 22, 2018_
